const quizDataAnalogi = [
    {
        question: '1. GEMPA : RITCHER = SUHU : ...',
        options: ['Termometer', 'Panas', 'Tekanan', 'Derajat'],
        answer: 'Derajat',
    },
    {
        question: '2. SENAPAN : BERBURU = ... : ...',
        options: ['Perangkap : Menangkap', 'Kapal : Berlabuh', 'Kereta : Lancar', 'Pancing : Ikan'],
        answer: 'Perangkap : Menangkap',
    },
    {
        question: '3. RAMALAN : KENYATAAN = ... : ...',
        options: ['Astrologi : Masa depan', 'Dugaan : Fakta', 'Mimpi : Tidur', 'Cita-cita : Angan-angan'],
        answer: 'Dugaan : Fakta',
    },
    {
        question: '4. UANG : PUNDI-PUNDI= ... : ...',
        options: ['Air : Tempayan', 'Gelas : Nampan', 'Hubungan : Jambang', 'Buku : Percetakan'],
        answer: 'Air : Tempayan',
    },
    {
        question: '5. RAMBUT: GUNDUL= ... : ...',
        options: ['Bulu : Cabut', 'Lantai : Licin', 'Pakaian : Bugil', 'Botak : Kepala'],
        answer: 'Pakaian : Bugil',
    },
    {
        question: '6. PENULIS : BUKU = ... : ...',
        options: ['Rumah : atap', 'Masinis : kereta api', 'Konsumen : produsen', 'Komponis : lagu'],
        answer: 'Komponis : lagu',
    },
    {
        question: '7. MANGGA : BUAH = ... : ...',
        options: ['Bunga : tangkai', 'Karya tulis : penjiplakan', 'Sapi : hewan', 'Sawah : petani'],
        answer: 'Sapi : hewan',
    },
    {
        question: '8. MATAHARI : TERIK = ... : ...',
        options: ['Panas : api', 'Bulan : benderang', 'Lampu : bersinar', 'Bumi : bulan'],
        answer: 'Bulan : benderang',
    },
    {
        question: '9. UANG : BANK = PADI : ...',
        options: ['Sawah', 'Kapas', 'Tempayan', 'Lumbung'],
        answer: 'Lumbung',
    },
    {
        question: '10. LAMPU : GELAP= MAKANAN:...',
        options: ['Lapar', 'Sakit', 'Kenyang', 'Penuh'],
        answer: 'Lapar',
    },
];